<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Linux on Jacob Rodal</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/tags/linux/</link><description>Recent content in Linux on Jacob Rodal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Jacob Rodal</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jrodal.com/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fix Gray Overlay When Video Sharing on Zoom</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/fix-zoom-gray-overlay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/fix-zoom-gray-overlay/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article describes a fix for a problem with the Picom/Compton compositor, which is often used with Linux window managers like i3 or qtile. The instructions in the article provide detailed steps on how to locate the configuration file and make the necessary changes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Deploy a Rocket Rust Web Application on VPS</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/how-to-deploy-rocket-rust-web-app-on-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/how-to-deploy-rocket-rust-web-app-on-vps/</guid><description>&lt;p>This tutorial provides a step-by-step guide on how to deploy a Rocket Rust web application on a VPS. The tutorial covers all the necessary steps, including acquiring a VPS and domain, setting up domain settings, downloading and installing necessary software on the VPS, and compiling the application. The tutorial also includes helpful tips and troubleshooting advice, making it a useful resource for anyone looking to deploy a Rocket Rust web application on a VPS.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dropdown/Scratchpad Terminals with i3</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/dropdown-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/dropdown-terminals/</guid><description>&lt;p>This tutorial provides a step-by-step guide on how to implement dropdown terminals in i3 using the scratchpad feature. The tutorial includes examples of how the dropdown terminals can be used and provides a detailed explanation of the necessary i3 configuration and accompanying script.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dunst Action</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/dunst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/dunst/</guid><description>&lt;p>This tutorial includes a description of Dunst and its capabilities, as well as a detailed explanation of the my Dunst screenshot actions, which include OCR, uploading to 0x0.st, deletion, renaming, and movement to/from clipboard.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Launching Scripts from a Smartwatch</title><link>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/watch-scripts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jrodal.com/posts/watch-scripts/</guid><description>&lt;p>This article explains how to execute shell commands on a Linux computer from an android smartphone and a WearOS smartwatch.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>